welocalize.com 2012-11-07

# Privacy - Welocalize: Translation | Localization | Internationalization

Protecting your privacy is important to Welocalize. We strive to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand the Welocalize Customer Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information.

## Why we collect personal information

Welocalize collects and uses your personal information to give you superior customer service, to provide you with convenient access to our products and services, and to make a wider range available to you. In addition, we use your personal information to keep you up to date on the latest service announcements, special offers, and other information we think you'd like to hear about. This may occasionally include information about products and services that can add value to your globalization strategy. From time to time, we may also use your personal information to contact you to participate in a market research survey, so that we can gauge customer satisfaction and develop better products.

## How we collect personal information

We collect information about you in several ways. For example, we might ask for your contact information when you correspond with us, call us to request service, participate in an online survey, or ask to be included in an email mailing list. We store the information you provide in a secure database.

## When we disclose personal information

At times we may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information. At any other time, if we are going to use your personal information differently from that stated at the time of collection, we will try to contact you via email using the most recent information we have. If you have not given us permission to communicate with you, you will not be contacted, nor will we use your personal information in a new manner.

## How we protect your personal information

Welocalize safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser. Welocalize portals use industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. To operate the Welocalize portals, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Netscape Navigator 3.0 or later, or Internet Explorer. This protects the confidentiality of your personal information while it is transmitted over the Internet.

## Access to your personal information

You always have access to the information we have about you from within the Welocalize portals. To review and update your personal contact information, simply click Profile button (Smile Face on the upper left corner on My Accounts Page. If you would like to review other personal information that Welocalize may have about you, email us at info@welocalize.com.

## Collecting other personal information

When you browse Welocalize's website, you are able to do so anonymously. Generally, we don't collect personal information when you browse - not even your email address. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us the type browser you are using, and which country you are visiting from.

Like many websites, the Welocalize website uses "cookie" technology. The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you. Cookies help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how long they spend there. We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our site so we can make the site even better.

## Our companywide commitment to privacy

To make sure your personal information remains confidential, we communicate these privacy guidelines to every Welocalize employee.

The Welocalize Customer Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.
